Greed digs the deepest graves
Never Grow Old is a western film directed by Ivan Kavanagh.
An Irish undertaker profits when outlaws take over a peaceful town, but his own
family come under threat as the death toll increases dramatically.
Patrick Tate, played by Emile Hirsch.
Christopher 'Dutch' Albert, played by John Cusack.
Audrey Tate, played by Déborah François.
Preacher Pike, played by Danny Webb.
Sheriff Parker, played by Tim Ahern.
Fred, played by Blake Berris.
Never Grow Old is a 2019 revisionist Western film
written and directed by Ivan Kavanagh.
It stars Emile Hirsch, Déborah François, John Cusack,
Danny Webb, Tim Ahern and Sam Louwyck.
Saban Films released the film on March 15.
The film explores themes of husband wife relationship,
oregon, usa, undertaker, preacher, frontier town.